quickbookmarks.com 2019-05-28

# Quick Bookmarks - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

QuickBookMarks.com ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use) tells you how we collect and process your personal data. We encourage you to read this policy to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

### What information we may collect from you

We may collect from you this personal information:

When you sign up for an account with us at www.quickbookmarks.com (our site), you provide us with your name, email and other personal information. We also collect data from you when you upload content to the site or when you report a problem with the site.  
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.  
We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. Typically, in surveys, [which you can complete online], this personal information about you will be collected: name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and occupation.  
Details of your visits to our site (traffic data, location data, and weblogs), which we keep for the purposes set out in this policy and other purposes.

### Cookies

We may collect information about your computer such as your ip address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about your browsing actions and does not personally identify you.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us improve our site and deliver a better and more personalized service. For example, they enable us to:

Estimate our audience size and usage pattern.  
Speed up your searches.  
Recognize you when you return to our site.   
Please note that through our cookies we store your user ID not your password.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

### Where we store your personal data

We may transfer or securely store your personal data. Your personal data may also be processed by staff, who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. Also remember the only information you have provided is your name and email address - you have not provided anything else.

All your personal information is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential, so please do not share it with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

### How we use your personal information

We use your personal information to:

Customize your experience on our site.  
Provide you with information on products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have given us consent to do so.  
Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.  
Notify you about changes to our service.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information where it is necessary to enforce our terms of use, policies and agreements, to fight fraud, to address security and technological issues and to protect our rights. We may also disclose your personal information when the law or the authorities require us to do so or if we sell all or part of our business.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

### Links

When you click on links on our site you may leave it. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

### Access to your information

You can update your personal information online by logging into your account and changing the personal information that is stored in your account.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can send an e-mail to support@quickbookmarks.com 

September 29, 2011
